Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Undergraduate and graduate studies, 1964-1995; 1987-1991; Series 1; 4 Linear Feet
  - GW, American Airports paper, interview (part III), 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Entertaining with the Washington Family, GW grad paper, 1990; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - GW dissertation (Thomas U. Walter), 1991; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - GW American Studies Program, 1987; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - GW Registration, 1987; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - GW Gelman Library, 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - GW student parking, 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - GW grades, 1988; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Univ. of VA, research paper, medieval history, 1965; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Univ. of VA magazine, article on Jefferson Society, 1965; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Univ. of VA book collecting award, 1965; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Univ. of VA article, student letters 1850s, 1965; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Univ. of South Carolina, Graduation, 1964; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Washington Sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2015; 2002-2008; Series 2; 15 Linear Feet
  Separated Materials note
  The following two books have been separated from the collection and are kept in the Special Collections stacks:
  James M. Goode. Washington Sculpture: A Cultural History of Outdoor Sculpture in the Nation's Capital. The Johns Hopkins University Press, 2009.
  James M. Goode. Outdoor Sculpture of Washington D.C. Smithsonian Books, 1979.
  Arranged into groups of like content. The series begins with folders labeled according to sculptures each folder title is preceeded by a number that is the system employed by Mr. Goode; they are ordered according to the book chapters. The sculpture folders are followed by other subject folders and research notes folders. Finally, the latter folders in this series contain drafts and proofs of the book. There are a few additional folders at the end from a 2017 acquisition.
  The materials of this series include manuscript drafts and proofs, research notes, clippings, photographs, correspondence, brochures, and reports. They range in date from circa 1970 to circa 2015, but the bulk of the material dates from 2002 to 2008. This series contains the material created and/or collected by James Goode in the process of writing Washington Sculpture: A Cultural History of Outdoor Sculpture in the Nation's Capital (The Johns Hopkins University Press, 2009).
  - Master lists of sculptures 2006 and 2007, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1.18 Supreme Court Lamb Pole Bases, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1.2 Progress of Railroading, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 1.27 Freedom, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1.29 Torch of Learning, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 1.3 Japanese-American Patriotism, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1.31 Cascade of Books, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1.38 Emancipation, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 1.39 Mary Bethune, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 1.40 Balance, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 1.41 Congressional Cemetery, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 1.48 John P. Sousa, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 1.6 Tragadily, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - 1.7 Compassion for the Axemen, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - 1 Add baseball stadium, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 1 - Taft Carillon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ch. 1 - Macomb Monument, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ch. 1 - Capitol Hill - not used - Dirksen House Off. building, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2.1 Farragut, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 2.2 Male Grey Wolf, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - 2.3 Nuns, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - 2.6 Sakharon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - 2.7 Belgrano, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - 2.15 Pandamania, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - 2.16 Zoo history, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - 2.16 Zoo Lions, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - 2.17 Mammoth and Mastodons, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 2.18 Reptile House Portal, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 2.19 Giant Anteater, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - 2.22 Happy Frog, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - 2.23 Gathering, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - 2.24 Uncle Beasley, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - 2 Omit Tomorrow, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - 2.28 De Fabricy, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - 2.29 Swan Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - 2.30 Muhlenberg, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Ch. 2 - Farragut, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ch. 2 - De Fabriczi (Conn. Ave), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ch. 2 - Home Rules, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 3.2 Sherman, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - 3.5 Butt-Millet Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 3.6 Boy Scout, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 3.8 Bulfinch Gatehouse, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 4 Introduction, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 4.14 Privilegium Obligatio, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 4.28 Law and Justice, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 4.29 Alex Shepherd, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 4.30 Bearing Witness, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 4.31 Federal Triangle Flowers, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 4.34 Bureaus of Dept. of Commerce, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Ch. 4 - Fidelity - Bravery - Integreity, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ch. 4 - Bearing Witness, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 5.2 Progress of Science, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 5.5 Einstein, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 5.8 O.A.S., circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 5.14 Daniel, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 5.15 R. Dario, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 5.17 C. Hull, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 5.18 Xochipilli, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 5.19 D.A.R., circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - 5.21 Red Cross Men and Women, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - 5.22 Delano, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - 5.23 Motherland, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - 5.24 Canova Lions, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - 5.26 Triple Arc I, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - 5.27 Rawlins, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - 5.28 San Martin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - 5.29 Bolivar, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - 5.32 Discus, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - 5.33 American Red Cross Nurses, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 5.34 American Red Cross Monument, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - 5.37 Rush, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - 5.38 America and War and Peace, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - 5.39 Don Quixote, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - 5.40 Galvez, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - 5.42 George Washington (bust), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 5.42 George Washington University, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - 5.42 George Washington (statue), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 5.45 Pushkin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 5.46 River Horse, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 5.48 Griffin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Ch. 6 Judiciary Square - introduction, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 6.1 Blackstone, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 6.3 She Who Must be Obeyed, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 6.7 Albert Pike, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 6.8 Guns into Plowshares, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 6.10 Columbia, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - 6.11 Lily Pond Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - 6.12 The Chess Players, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - 6.13 John Marshall, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - 6.16 National Law Enforcement Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - 6.17 Civil War Frieze, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - 6.18 Boundary Markers, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - 6.19 Tool de Force, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - 6.21 Verdi, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - 6.22 Slow Rondo, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - 6.23 Electricity, Fid., and Steam, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - 6.25 Vaquero, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - 6.26 Epoch, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 6.27 Party Animals, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - 6.29 Richard Hunt Sculpture Plaza, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - 6.30 The Extra Mile, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Ch. 6 - Slow Rondo, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 6 - Civil War frieze, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ch. 7 - Three Servicemen, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Ch. 7 - the mall introduction, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 7 - Signers of the Declaration of Independence (not used), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 7.2 Grant, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 7.4 Knife Edge Mirror, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 7.5 Roof, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 7.7 Ad Astra, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 7.7 Delta Solar, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 7.9 Continuum, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 7.10 introduction - Hirshhorn Museum, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 7.10 The Burgers of Calais, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 7.11 Horse and Rider, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 7.12 The Last Conservation Piece, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 7.13 Thinker on a Rock, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 7.14 Typewriter Eraser, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 7.15 Colossal Head No. 4, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 7.16 Columbia Protecting Science and Industry, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 7.18 Spencer Baird, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 7.19 Andrew Jackson Downing Urn, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 7.20 Saint Dunstan, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 7.22 Infinity, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 7.23 Ewenfritz, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 7.26 World War II Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 7.27 Korean War Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 7.28 Three Vietnam Servicemen Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 7.29 Vietnam Womens' Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 8 - Eibran, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 8.1 Victims of Communism, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 8.5 Gen. John Logan, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 8.6 Gen. James McPherson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 8.8 Gen. Geo. Thomas, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 8.9 Martin Luther, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 8.11 Sky Landscape, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 8.12 Gen. Win. Scott, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 8.16 Salamander, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 8.17 Victorian House Carvings, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 8.18 Neoclassical House Carvings, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 8.21 Baraque Bird, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 8.21 Mahatama Ghandi, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 8.26 Thomas Masaryk, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 8.27 T. Shevchenko, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 8.28 Vassil Levsky, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 8.29 Dumbarton Bridge Sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 8.30 Gibran, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 8.31 St. Jerome, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 8.33 African Elephant, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 8.34 Mustafa Ataturk, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 8.35 Asian Elephant, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 8.36 Kahil Gibran, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 8.38 Crown Princess Martha, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 8.39 Ch. Lindbergh, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 8.40 Behrend Menorah, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 8.41 Gen. Artemas Ward, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 8.42 Akhenaten, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 8.44 John Wesley, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 8.45 Pomona (and Torso Sheaf), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 8.47 Gen. F. Von Steuben, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Ch. 9 N. Capitol Street introduction, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 9.4 A Bridge Across the Beyond, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 9.8 Gen. W. Scott, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 9.11 John Lenthal Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 9.12 Adams Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 9.18 Progress of the Negro Race, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 9.22 Great Men from the Order of Saint Francis, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 9.24 Pope John Paul, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 9 Mermaid (not included), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 9 Christ (removed), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 9 Armillary Sphere (not used), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ch. 10 - Navy Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ch. 10 - Kosciuszko, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ch. 10 - Around the Void, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 10.1 Gen. Geo. Meade, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 10.2 Spirit of Haida Gwaii, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 10.3 Mellon Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 10.4 Temperance Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 10.6 Gen. Hancock, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 10.7 Navy Memorial part A, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 10.7 Navy Memorial part B, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 10.9 Benj. Franklin, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 10.11 Gen. Pershing, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 10.12 Bex Eagle, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 10.14 Whitney Mus. Eagle, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 10.15 Gen. Lafayette, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 10.16 Gen. Kosciuszko, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 10.18 Gen. A. Jackson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 10.20 Gen. von Steuben, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 10.21 War Pediment, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 10.25 Wedlock, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 10.26 The Observer, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 10.27 Geo. Washington (eques. statue), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 10.28 Soloman's Gate, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 11 Potomac Park, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 11 The Awakening, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 11.2 Cuban Friendship Urn, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 11.3 George Mason, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 11.4 Drafting the Declaration of Independence, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 11.5 Thomas Jefferson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 11.8 Loss and Regeneration, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 11.9 M.L. King, Jr. (part 1), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 11.9 M.L. King, Jr. (part 2), circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 11.10 FDR Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 11.10 FDR Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 11.10 FDR Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 11.13 Social Programs, FDR, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 11.21 Arts of War, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 11.23 Arts of Peace, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 11 King, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 12.2 Eolden Warrior Prince, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 12.3 Whopping Cranes, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 12.4 American Wildlife, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12.5 Future Stars, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 12.9 Spirit of Freedom, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 12.10 James Buchanan, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 12.13 Serenity, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 12.14 E. Zapata, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 12.18 Mount Pleasant Call Box, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 12.19 25rd N.Y. Cav. Regiment, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 12.20 The Spirit of Paul Robeson, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 12.20 Library Stars, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 12.21 Walter Reed, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 12 - National Shrine, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ch. 12 - Spirit of Freedom, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 13 Southwest, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 13.1 Titantic, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 13.2 Maine Lobster, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 13.3 Bartholdi Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 13.4 American Veterand Disabled for Life Memorial, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 13.5 Aeroic Shorepoints, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 13.8 Earth Energy, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 13.9 Heating Plant Machinery, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - M-10 Thomas A. Edition, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 14 Wisconsin Avenue, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Ch. 14 Washington National Cathedral, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Ch. 14 The Creation, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Ch. 14 The Creation: Adam, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ch. 14 Washington National Cath. Carillon and other DC carillons, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 14.1 Stag Minos, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 14.2 Man Helping Man, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - 14.3 William D. Douglas, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - 14.4 Helix Fountain, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 14.5 Illuminated Crowd, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 14.7 F. S. Key, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 14.9-13 Oak Hill Cem, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 14.9 Wm. Pinckney, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 14.11 John H. Payne, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 14.14 Ex Nihilo, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 14.15 Adam, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 14.16 West Gates, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 14.18 Gareoyles, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 15 Maryland suburbs, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 15.1 Armillary Sphere, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 15.2 Time Is Up, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 15.5 Bethesda sculpture, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 15.5 Madonna of the Trail, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 15.6 Lyrical Lady, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 15.9 B-Tree, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 15.10 Sky Horizon, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 15.12 Hiawatha, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 15.14 Strathmore Hall, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 15.14 Praying Mantis, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 15.15 Granddaughters, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 15.16 Familia, circa 1970 - circa 2008; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 20)